UNESCO Second Canadian Archaeological Expedition to Carthage Records MS210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Excavation site images, 1905 -- 2002; MS210.004; 7.45 Linear Feet; 1424 Digital Object(s)
  - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.005
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016 (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 20KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00016.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017 (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00017.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018 (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 23KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00018.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019 (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00019.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020 (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 25KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00020.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021 (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 26KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00021.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022 (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00022.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023 (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 27KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00023.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024 (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00024.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025 (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 29KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00025.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026 (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00026.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027 (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 34KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00027.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028 (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 35KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00028.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029 (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00029.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030 (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 36KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00030.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
    - 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031 (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 3)
      - 37KR 2CC79, 1979; MS210.004.003.00031.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 3)